William B. Gould IV Correspondence 6412
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
William B. Gould IV Correspondence
1965-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gould, William B., IV
Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel
6412
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Correspondence.
Correspondence from Mr. Gould's time with the New York law firm of Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel. From 1965 to 1968 Mr. Gould worked there under Theodore W. Kheel, Samuel Pierce, and Morris Lasker.
9392987
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 31, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 31, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Gould, William B., IV; Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel
9392987
- Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  February 1972
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  May-August 1968
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  January-February 1968
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  December 1967
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  November 1967
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  September-October 1967
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  August 1967
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  March-July 1967
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  January-February 1967
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  October-December 1966
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  August-September 1966
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  June-July 1966
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  April-May 1966
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  February-March 1966
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  January 1966
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  November-December 1965
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  July-October 1965
- Battle, Fowler, Stokes & Kheel Memoranda, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  July-September 1965